WAMOTO TIMOTHY.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER.

PROFILE

An enthusiast and steady-growing individual applying for the role of a software engineer with the Uganda Revenue Authority. Has Two years of experience as a software engineer, developing web applications and management software solutions for the Organization. Possesses excellent interpersonal qualities and an extensive range of technical skills, including Object Oriented Programming, programming languages, debugging, testing and deployment tasks.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+256-782537793

EMAIL:

wamototimothy@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Coding. Football. Gaming. Mind Games.

EDUCATION

Makerere University.

2019 - 2022.

Bachelor of Information Systems and Technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mengo Hospital – Internship.

July 2021 - October 2021.

I offered help and support to the system users at the hospital which resulted into effective use of technologies, improved productivity and subsequently, reduced friction.

Mengo Hospital - End User Support.

December 2021 - August 2022.

I was retained to continue with the great work and support I was extending.

Uganda Revenue Authority – Software Developer.

August 2022 - To Date.

- Developments on the Instant TIN API whose purpose is to expand Taxpayer registration through enhancing the TIN acquisition and making the validation process simple, secure and Instant for Individuals and Businesses/Entities.
- Developments on the Etax ISSP service.
- Developments on the new Litigation/Legal Information System (LIMAS), a web-based application designed to help the URA Legal Department track all the activities within the department domain from creation to completion.

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

Integrating services and components, C#, React, Oracle, SQL Server, Git, Software Development Life cycle, Developing web applications, Identifying and debugging issues.

Soft Skills:

Adaptability, Problem-solving, Attention to detail, Organisation, Teamwork, Empathy, Teamwork, Collaboration, Patience, Critical thinking, Time management.

CERTIFICATES

CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Networks, 2019.

REFERENCE.

Mr. Alex Daniel Wamono: Supervisor, Software Engineering. Uganda Revenue Authority. +256-779602570. awamono@ura.go.ug.